

Prasenjit Pawar Analyst/Software Engineer



I have excellent communication skills, an eye for detail, and a B. Tech degree in Computer Science and Engineering. I have done certifications to improve my knowledge and skills, and internships to learn and understand how to implement my skills, which enhanced my experience and learning.



KEY SKILLS -

- Problem solving and logical thinking
- Data Structure
- Python
- Linux
- React fundamentals (JSX, Virtual Dom, Native)

8669106099



EXPERIENCE -

ANALYST

(May 2022 - Present) **CAPGEMINI** - Mumbai

MERN STACK DEVELOPER INTERN

(Mar 2022 - MAY 2022)

ACROSS THE GLOBE (ATG)—Bengaluru, India

- Developed responsive mobile application for both android and iOS according to the clients need.
- Worked on developing various fully responsive websites. while working with the sales team.
- Added responsive components for the applications.

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP

(Jan 2022 - Mar 2022)

CONQ FZE - FREEZONE ESTABLISHMENT

- Designed and developed multiple backend API using Python/Django, MySQL.
- Created reusable, modular, frontend components/pages in Vue.js



PROJECTS

CIVIQUE: USING SOCIAL MEDIA TO DETECT URBAN EMERGENCY

(Nov 2021 - June 2021)

We present the Civique system for Emergency detection in urban areas by monitoring blogs micro like Tweets.

RESTAURANT MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

(Aug 2017 – Apr 2018)

Developed a Restaurant management system using HTML, CSS and PHP.



EDUCATION

B. Tech

(2018-2021)

MARATHWADA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Specialization – Computer Science and Engineering

DIPLOMA

(2015-2018)

P.E.S POLYTECHNIC

Specialization-Computer Engineering



CERTIFICATIONS

Python Programming	Digitize IT Station
Artificial Intelligence	Udemy
AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner	

prasenjitpawar22@gmail.com